HOSSAM SAID



hossam11said@gmail.com



01141729425



linkedin.com/in/hossam-said-815496195



https://hoss11h.github.io/website/

Summary

I am Front-End Developer With 2 Years Experience In Developing And Building Exceptional, High-Quality, Performant, Responsive Websites And Web Applications.

I Developed Many Websites With Trending Styles And

Features In UI & UX Besides Caring About Performance, Code Efficiency, And The User Experience.

Some Of My Work Was Published On Themeforest And Got Great Feedback.

I Work With The Famous Libraries & Frameworks (React, Redux, Material Ui, Next js, Tailwind, Bootstrap With Vanilla Js. That Does not Hold Me From Learning New Things To Keep Up With The New Technologies In Our Field.

Experience



Frontend Developer

Zythemes

Feb 2021 - Present (9 months +)

Made Pixel Perfect themes

Created Stunning Landing Pages & Delivered The Best UI & UX Experience

Produced Websites Compatible with Multiple Browsers With The Help Of JavaScript and other libraries & Tools.

p Frontend Developer

Upwork

Jun 2020 - Present (1 year 5 months +)

I made bunch of websites for clients from all over the world and helped others with problems to fix and improve their websites.

I got good ratings from them for the quality and discipline of my work and they were very happy with the results



Frontend Developer

Zytheme

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020 (4 months)

Made Pixel Perfect themes Created Stunning Landing Pages Delivered The Best Ui & UX Experience Produced Websites Compatible with Multiple Browsers. Used programming capabilities in JavaScript and other libraries.

Education



Zagazig University

Bachelor's degree, Business/Commerce, General 2018 - 2022

Skills

SASS • JavaScript • Bootstrap • HTML5 • Git • React.js • Redux.js • Next.js • Tailwind CSS • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS)